No, from the morning breeze
I haven't even washed my face yet
Where are you going like that?
Either say something or leave now...
mister!
Are you really that guy? really
Are you really my Mr. Kim?
It's really you, Mr. Kim.
- Man!
- Oh my.
Did you bring him here?
How much are you like this oppa?
I need to know that I'm doing my best
Well then, uncle, from now on
Are you still with me? uh?
I hope so
Kyung-do came and begged me so much.
But why the highlight?
Didn’t you come?
hey… Getting older
How do you do that!
I don't know the event, I don't know the event
How do I do this, this
Your body is a gift
Don't you do that?
You matched your personal color too.
Give it to me
- Do you do this?
- Just once
- Okay, do it, do it.
- Do it, do it?
- ruler… So pretty, huh?
- okay?
It suits you well, man.
- Really?
- Oh, absolutely!
you… Okay then
Where should we take you?
uncle
Did you see the article about my divorce?
Baby, I saw it, well done, well done, very
Just in today’s style
Living freely
If you think it's not true
Just meet someone else
Honestly, with this beauty
I can't go three times, get married?
I think so too.
Beauty is a waste
Hey, not three times.
But, with Gyeongdo and Mr.
I guess we kept in touch and met each other.
You both miss me so much
Right?
Teacher Seongjun Lee, No. 1241…
huh?
- mister!
- Uh
I thought it was you
On the way passing by
Thank you, man, but…
This is okay
Take it, I received a lot of severance pay.
Severance pay?
I quit, that's it.
Not long
I buy things for my parents to cheer up.
thank you
It's hardness
I live it called life
Well, you're out of breath, aren't you?
Still, you have to be strong to survive
- I'll go, eat well.
- Yes
It's hardness
Huh?
Thank you so much for bringing me here.
I never even thought about it
This oppa is all for you...
Let's take a look at the press release photos.
Huh?
Ah, today
I want to sleep after watching this, ah...
It's hardness
Is it longitude?
If you get hit once
We're both hurting, right?
Let's be good at speaking, okay?
Hey, cell phone picture quality these days.
How good is it?
Let's just do a few good chapters, okay?
I love you, Gyeongdo, huh? huh? huh?
This is a crooked love
I love you, Gyeongdo, okay?
huh? huh?
How, one more turn?
When Jiwoo was young
Did you learn about energy saving?
I'm nervous for my first day at work, I'm nervous, but
Now, I've done five laps
If this is going to happen, from next time just
Take the bus, subway is also good
Man, hurry up
i want to go to the bathroom
Oh my, that's right
Why are you pouring coffee like this?
- Uh, hello?
- We'll be there soon, focus.
Uh, hey, hey…
It's me
- I'll go.
- Fighting!
just one more time
Oh, but even things like this
Isn’t that a bit much to order something to do?
It's pretty, but it's also very pretty.
- Jarim Apparel Public Relations Department works hard
- What is it?
'Director Seo Ji-woo
‘Jarim Apparel’s first step’, this
Well, it came out good.
Hey, I got one of these.
One public relations employee
I must have angled my knees so that they went out.
Was it taken by a public relations employee?
Did someone out of love take the picture?
Eh?
to?
What are you talking about, Mr.
- Hello?
- Oh, yeah.
Well, last time
Request for ingredient analysis
- I contacted you after the results came out.
- Oh, yes.
Didroxin?
Yes, the drug ingredient was detected.
Uh… What is the drug used for?
For patients with stick syndrome
It's a prescribed medicine.
Stick syndrome?
It's a type of chronic vascular disease.
As for the disease itself, if you take the medicine well,
There's no danger
There is nothing to worry about with this drug
It's not toxic
However, if you overdose
There are some side effects
Consult carefully with your doctor
It's a prescribed medicine.
Uh, so what are the side effects?
hmm… Memory loss, cognitive impairment
Common symptoms of Alzheimer's
The problem is the drug level
It came out pretty high.
Oh, yes, Mr. President, it's me.
please take a moment
yes
thank you
Wait a minute
What the secretaries give
don't drink anymore
Ah…
Last time I took it
I mean coffee
I'm going to take it and drink it.
Ah, yes, that
Actually, I left it to you to test the ingredients.
Do you have any didroxine tablets?
Are you taking it?
Didroxin…
It looks like a medicine I took before.
I am now prescribed a different medication.
- But why...
- uh…
Why did you change the medicine?
May I ask you a question?
Uh, at that time, I went abroad
I went on a business trip
my husband is a doctor
I think we said we would meet
Because better drugs have been released
Prescribe some medicine
He said he wanted to change it.
Didn’t you hear the explanation directly?
yes
What was wrong with the drug?
Oh, the drug itself isn't bad.
Side effects may occur
Looking for papers, medical field
I also asked reporters for advice.
CEO, symptoms of Alzheimer’s
I think it's related
Why is that in coffee?
Who is that…
No way
Could it be that that person...
Because it's not certain
Still, first of all
I think you need to be careful.
Drinks or food given by Secretary Yu
Do not eat it
But if you give it to me as is
Because you might notice
until evidence is found
- Must be natural
- Yes
Put a camera in the bathroom
I want it installed
yes
There are more and more things to be thankful for
How do I repay all this debt?
Reporter: What am I doing?
I didn't know you were unwell.
It's a disease that just needs to be taken well.
There is no disruption to daily life
It's not a fatal disease
How about discussing it with Jiwoo as well?
- Jiwoo also needs to know…
- I will.
We need to discuss it
Ah… Do you want to go see Jiwoo?
If you know I'm here
I don't think it will work
Huh?
- Wait at home.
- I just arrived.
Uncle, you had a hard time, right?
Get rid of your anxiety about going to work
You’re a senior office worker.
Manager, I'm going in.
Please enter carefully, Driver Kim.
Please go in
- Shall we go?
- Yes
Were you scared of your first day at work?
Hey, don't say anything, in front of the company
Did you do about five laps?
In a country where there is not a single drop of oil?
I thought it was Mr. Kim.
The man said to take the bus next time
Hey, public transportation too
You have to be smart to ride it
You're so foolish
Anywhere, crying and screaming
‘Oh, I got off by mistake, please come pick me up.’
Hey, you go home.
- Go, go somewhere else, not here.
- 'Uh, how do I get home?'
Huh? go somewhere else
Watch out for stairs, watch out for cars
Jinwoo has to go to Taekwondo right away.
- If you run away again, you will live here.
- Yes!
Uh, okay, bye!
- yes!
- Guys, be careful.
Hyobin, hello
Uh, mom is coming later.
With Dongwon
- They said they were going out and having dinner.
- Wow!
- Uh, did you finish that?
- Uh, in there.
inside, inside
My wife is inside.
- Oh, is this it?
- Uh
I'm asking for everything
Hey, Seo Ji-woo, what are you doing?
Are you a duchess?
- What do you mean by portrait, portrait artist?
- I got a lot.
It was the best painting I've ever received.
Boy, I just threw it
The deposit was made
- Did you do your best?
- Grinded the bones.
Even hardness as a free gift
I shouldn't have drawn it for you
- I didn't think of that.
- Wow, I don't care about service.
Our Wooshik should have started a business.
Hey, why are you doing this, conductor?
Why?
Honestly, the reporter keeps saying
Asking who you are is a bit...
The informant is Kang Min-woo.
Kang Min-woo… Who is that?
article by you and dahye
Kang Min-woo gave it to me.
Jalim Apparel CEO Seo Ji-yeon's husband
The deal he reported?
What are you?
- I didn't get it from that person.
- Then who is it?
Huh?
Mr. Lee, hey, don’t you know me?
Because you are not honest
- Can you open this door and get out?
- I'm going crazy.
Quick! Got it, quick
If you can't talk because you're embarrassed, just say it
Let me just sneak a peek, really.
- Quick?
- Yes, quick, quick!
So Reporter Nam is Reporter Choi.
Support and interview
And after it's over
Email me...
- Where are you looking?
-Where is the entertainment department?
Please give it to me
I'm an entertainment reporter.
- Here's the sign.
- Oh, yeah.
- thank you
- Yes
- Then, contact me, Reporter Choi.
So, I came to the entertainment department
You swallowed the report.
But, the conductor who sells it
Did you avoid it because you didn’t like it?
Why do I hate my brother?
How much do you love me?
I was afraid the manager would be embarrassed, so I stayed silent.
What does this mean again?
I told the manager
I reported it, but
I hope the manager doesn't do it.
seriously
I feel wronged
Until then, my brother, Seo Ji-woo, and Cho Jin-eon
I didn't know we were so connected
Since the manager knows everything, I probably stopped him.
Reporter pretending not to know the report
I think it's media corruption
What did I do wrong?
Did you just gulp down the scoop?
Honestly, I wish my brother got it first
Isn't this just a kill?
The manager told me not to use it?
That's enough now, right?
So now, stop bothering me
- Can I leave?
- sit down
- It starts now, where are we going?
-Why again?
- We need to do follow-up coverage.
- Yes?
Now, focus.
The report turned out to be even more vicious.
If it was the starting point for making money
Can you be free?
Why are you so scary? What starting point?
I can't explain it now
First, let’s go meet Ah Da-hye with me.
Because Ahn is looking for you
You apply for a meeting
Are you asking me to meet Ahn?
Are you crazy, bro?
Why are you surprised?
Uh, Doo-jin is doing follow-up coverage.
Dahye Ah
I don't know what it is, but don't do it, don't do it
If the manager doesn't do it, then
You shouldn't do it, yeah
- I'll go first.
- Mr. Lee
What does this mean?
Was this the manager’s?
Hey, I'll organize it and report it to you.
Ah!
- I heard you told me not to use it?
- what?
That article, Cho Jin-eon
Move over, I don't remember
You're so loyal
The manager is definitely an F.
Capital F, passing by
I did it because I wanted to do it.
It's not something to leave here.
Right, Jiwoo?
brother
You know it was the tower of the Gyeonggi Province Ministry of Culture, right?
I know it was the Ministry of Culture.
Such a masterpiece
Top tier should stay at home, it's perfect
Isn't that right, sister?
Isn’t this kind of a masterpiece?
I'm out of luck, when will the meat arrive?
- When is Gyeongdo coming?
- I don't know.
Ah, brother
Then eat that one first
- I bought it for Dongwon.
- If it’s Jiwoo Pick,
Luxurious and delicious
That’s what it is, right?
- They said meat is coming, eat it and eat it.
- Yes
- Wow, you’re pretty.
- Ah, thank you.
- What is it?
- Eat and eat.
Jeongmin!
Fish oil, milk, mother
Baby, please give it to me, please give it to me
- It's not heavy.
- Baby, please.
Gyeongdo calls his friends
Are you the last one?
Are you here yet?
They told me to ask for kimchi just because you guys are coming.
He said he was coming to pick it up but he was late.
I don't have time and I'm old
I brought it, well, what should I do?
Hey, when I saw it
Because I want to take care of my mother
I think I'm late on purpose
It’s been a while since we last saw each other again
Gyeongdo is deep in thought.
Ugh, this…
Hang out with yourselves, what do you wear?
Do you ever want to be a mama's boy?
Kyung-do, he has hope for the future
You're a mama's boy, right?
- Let's go, kid, let's go in.
- Oh my, oh my...
Be loud, have fun
- Oh, then... child
- Yes, yes, I'm going.
I'll eat it deliciously! Please go in
- What is this?
- My mother gave it to me, it's called kimchi.
- Kyung-do hasn’t arrived yet?
- Yes
No, I don't have a landlord, so what...
No, what is this again? uh?
Hey, Jiwoo, kinda…
Hey, the picture painted by the top tier is
A little different, huh?
Seyoung's talent wasted
This is how you're going to do it, huh?
draw me, draw me
- When I receive the deposit, I wet the brush.
- Right.
Hey, Jiwoo again
How much did you deposit? huh?
- Where did you go?
- what?
- Jiwoo
Is Jiwoo in the bathroom?
huh?
Looking for laundry?
uh… Hello, me
It hasn't cooled down even after packaging. It looks delicious.
Where did Jiwoo go?
There you are, graceful
They say it will come soon
I guess he went to buy something in front of here.
- Eat quickly, you too.
- Oh, I'm hungry.
Mmm, delicious
You must have bought it because it was delicious.
- Why is this guy crooked?
- AC
Hey, in human terms, that's
Isn’t it a comedy? uh?
Leave it like that
Do you want to live, Lee Kyung-do?
People or things are better
The picture is better, or so it should be.
But is this real or a photo?
I can't hear anything
That's just in the picture
Because I put it in, it’s art.
Isn’t this rare?
It's so delicious, why don't you eat it?
i eat everything
Isn’t this kind of thing a bit rare?
tooth… Is it delicious?
- Let's eat
- Delicious!
- that… When you go to the department store
- Yes, a department store.
If you go down there...
- Oh, there's a food section in the basement...
- Yes
Pretty looking things to eat
- There are so many.
- Yes, there are a lot of them.
Is technology good these days?
It looks pretty and tastes good too.
That's just what it looks like
I thought it would taste good
I bought one and tried it and it was delicious.
So it will be sold in department stores.
Yes, desserts these days
It came out really well
The price is the price of a meal
-There were tons of them.
- Some are more expensive than Jjajangmyeon
Because something like this takes a lot of effort
Making bread isn't easy
Should I pay for the laundry?
I was thinking about opening a bakery.
I was trying to learn how to make this pastry.
Oh, I can't do it, it's difficult
Well, kneading the dough
It's very difficult...
- I heard, me too.
- Yes
Gyeongdo will find it, I have to go quickly.
Oh, my, my...
that…
How do I call you
I don't know if I should do it.
- Me?
- yes…
kid, that
If you watch something like a drama,
Someone I don't like
If you call me mother
‘Why am I your mother?’
And things like that
I've seen it a few times
It's funny to call you 'Ajumma'
Seyoung and the kids too
Everyone calls me mother
Just, just take it easy.
I will also speak comfortably
thank you
It's not someone I don't like
Oh my
This is what's left
I guess I should say that you enjoy it too, Dad.
I will buy it again next time
Delicious food in the basement of the department store
I'll buy it
It looks pretty too
Uh, uh... Mother
I… hardness
Because various things have happened
We met again
That… I have shame
I have no choice.
Gyeongdo is right in front of you
‘Don’t do that, don’t lose your mind’
That doesn't work.
sorry
There is a late-night getaway in every neighborhood
Why would it happen?
Because I have no choice
It just pops out.
Come on, I know a shortcut.
I'll take you there, go
sorry
I laugh so much...
Oh my, how can you two clean this up?
Let's clean it up together
Two? One guy will clean it up
Baby, please draw Jeongmin too
Hey, this is 10 years old.
10 years old, this
Just deposit the money, here we go.
Congratulations on Jiwoo’s first day at work
- congratulations!
-What was the last time we got together?
- Isn’t that also a celebration of going to work?
- If you're going to be like this, just go to sleep.
Just shake everything off and go
I ate it with my height, I noticed it
Hey, hurry up, hurry up and get to work
- Wow, really!
- 진짜 빨리, 아유, 새끼야
진짜, 빨리 가
갈게, 축하한다
- 먼저 갈게!
- No, I said stay with me and leave.
- Okay, it's okay, it's okay, come quickly.
- No, let's play a little more.
- Put your shoes on, shoes
-You can sleep on the street.
Come on, hurry up, come on, let's go, let's go
Well, hello!
The earth seems quiet
Wow, hey...
Uh, you sit down and relax.
Rest, rest, rest
- Is that so?
- Yes
Oh my
What did you do with mom?
Wow, how did you know?
You are holding Dongwon’s cupcake.
Where could they have gone?
Hey, after all, a reporter is a reporter.
There's a party
What did you do?
Um…
eat cupcakes
Let's have a chat, then take me with you.
What are you talking about?
A story about dessert in the basement corner of a department store?
- huh?
- Mom and me
The humor code fits well.
I have a very important meeting tomorrow
All the scary executives are gathered together
-What's on the agenda?
- Manjar theorem
Manjar?
Manjar is our home.
It’s a symbol, Director Seo.
The former Chairman’s favorite
You know it's a line.
yes, i know very well
But, every year, sales
It's a downward curve
Now we have to face it
At least it’s an outlet rather than a store
From 2 to 3 years ago, home shopping sales began.
I'm in a situation where I'm leaning
Even the representative
Is this something you agree to?
The idea of ​​organizing the manjar
Does it feel like you're saying to erase your father?
A little, uh... Kinda like that, right?
That's not what you say, so don't do it.
Jarim has been responsible for the second generation
The CEO is Seo Ji-yeon.
Just a little bit and I won't get into trouble
Dad might be Jiwoo
I guess you needed something like this
Without being tied down
Face it face to face, be bold
Let's buy it and try it
Fine dining restaurant
Let's try it
Korea is also high end
Must have a luxury brand
It all started with Jarim Apparel.
I think we should open it
high-end luxury brand
considerable time and
Don't you need capital?
That's right, from now on
Let’s start step by step
Even when I turn 60, I can't guarantee it.
If you bring a famous designer
I think we have a chance
I have a feasible plan
I want you to put it out there
Ah…
I understand that you feel unfamiliar and anxious.
I am also a new employee now.
I can't help but feel excited...
It may be unrealistic
Create a specific direction
I will present it
‘Specific’…
Ah
Fighting, Mr. Manager.
thank you
Uh… There is nothing wrong
If you take the medicine consistently,
Well, in the future, in a big way
I don't think you need to worry
Changing the treatment medication
Do you think it would be more effective?
What about didroxin, which was prescribed in the past?
The effectiveness of the drug does not decrease or decrease.
However, there was an issue with side effects.
Oh, I heard it from my husband.
It's leaking
what side effects
Was there a concern?
of this central nervous system
As the damage begins
I have a cure
I suggested changing it.
He was probably on a business trip overseas at the time.
I think you didn't come to the hospital right away.
That's right, I remember
Fortunately, the side effects were resolved early on.
Still, recovery was possible.
If you keep taking it, you'll get Alzheimer's disease.
I could have gone
Fortunately…
Then 6 months later
I'll get you treatment.
thank you
- Ah, teacher.
- Yes
If I take that drug
If I had taken more
Is recovery difficult?
If Alzheimer's has already progressed
Can't I recover?
If you recognize it and stop taking it
It doesn't get any worse
And it was almost the beginning at that time.
You don't have to worry too much
Are you still a little anxious?
then how
Can I help you with the examination again?
No, just
I feel dizzy when I think about it.
thank you
Hey, look at this.
This is now
This is a list of current designers...
Ah, why are you like this?
Manjar's father
He said it’s a line he cherishes.
How to do manjar
Can you organize it?
Oh, I'm talking about this
I hear it too much, really.
This guy has no blood or tears
Oh, okay, look at this.
This person is Lucas and this time
Bye bye for the last time in SS season
Then, this old man
Are you scouting?
This grandpa is so big
So this guy
- Successor?
- There are two assistant managers on Lucas’ team.
One of them is Bella Jean.
This person is the successor
If you're nominated, there's already a deal or something.
Isn't it over?
This person is of Korean descent, his nationality is Australian.
First, add patriotism...
Are you adding patriotism to anything?
And when it comes to the Pirco brand,
A Korean designer
Became chief designer
This also has meaning
Ah, in this spirit
How is the reporter doing?
Dongwoon Ilbo, this won’t work.
The conductor is complacent and addicted
Do you want a scoop?
you said it well
Bella Jean or Lucas
What does this have to do with a reporter from Dongwoon Ilbo?
- Let’s order some chicken.
- then
Your relationship is groundless
When creating a disjointed article
You didn't read the article properly, did you?
I am such a cowardly word that is not true
I never wrote it
Oh, that's right, anyway
Your company at that time
Fashion magazine editor-in-chief, do you understand?
Let's order some chicken
What am I, a Zarim employee?
- Boy, I'm slowly losing my temper, this is it.
- Have you ever seen Jiwoo in the military?
Ah, next week in Samseong-dong
All the fashion giants are gathered here
I have to go there
Bella Jean might come
Then you too are a resident.
Come on in, I'm hungry!
How can you pretend to be a resident?
IC
That's a relief
It's not getting serious anymore
I don't want to tell Jiwoo.
So to Jiwoo
Tell me more...
Jiwoo now
I'm working on an important project.
I don't know if it's my mood
I’m in good condition these days
Later, when Jiwoo takes a breather
Well, back then
They say a good night’s sleep is good for recovery.
where in the paper
It's so obvious, but still
Because you need to recover completely quickly.
sleep, sleep well
Yeah, ah, nothing to say, yeah
- Is anyone sick?
- I'm surprised, Icy.
Stop it, you'll be sick.
Hey, you know Editor-in-Chief Ga-eul Kim, right?
I don't know, I don't even know each other
Collaboration on articles was also done with the manager.
I didn't do it, you don't know
Like you
I thought you didn't know
How can you be proud of something you don’t know?
Give strength to your eyes, Mr.
It doesn't help anyway, kid.
What if luxury company officials gather together?
Looking at the outlook for the luxury goods business
Following Kim Ga-eul
It's best to just fit in.
Ah! Hankyung has an older sister.
I also had a good time, huh?
Leave this to the manager
I fell asleep after discussing it with the conductor.
What are you tired of, Lee Kyung? Does your stomach hurt?
I do various things
Thanks to Jiwoo, Louis special article
It went well, didn't it?
Wait, so what?
Then we are there too
They say they need help. I need to help them.
It's not us, it's you
no, what are we
Are you a journalist who works like this?
If you get one, you can’t give two.
Can’t you do this one thing?
Jingle jingle really...
What are you curious about?
Well, first of all...
First of all, what?
Hey, look at this.
This is it, hey, this is pretty, uh
- Is your body different?
- ah…
White is fine, let’s go with this
Are you really buying it for me?
If you miss the motorcycle rental fee
Are you saying you won't get much?
Hey, hey, don't do this though.
This is too strong, don't do it
Even in the delivery world
There is such a thing as momentum
If you give me something like this
No one can attack me?
Even now, no one is attacking me
Oh my, you really don't like it?
Are you going to accept this?
White, white is pretty
Isn’t white pretty?
It's an investment, if you do well later
I really need to get the manager to do it.
If you look at it, you are on the enter side
It suits you so well
You are really good at investing.
Representative Lee
It's all thanks to actor Cha.
- Actor Cha has to be popular, huh?
- Thank you, yes, I understand!
Why did you meet with my company's lawyers?
I met you to get some legal advice.
All the noisy issues have been sorted out.
What are you asking yourself?
- Did you have an accident again?
- Oh, no, no, I
How quiet these days
I only do exercise for a living.
So what's the problem? uh?
I have to be honest
Help what you need to help
What needs to be sorted out is not to be sorted out.
Ah, yes
Father, I…
Father, I am Jiwoorang.
I want to live well again
I should have lived well a long time ago
But there
Why do you need legal advice?
- I can't go down on my knees and beg.
- No, that's why I...
Can I file for divorce?
Because I was asking
Back off?
Yes, father, I feel really wronged.
Seo Ji-woo wants to divorce me.
I made it all up with my boyfriend and now...
my… My lover?
- Oh, no, no.
- My lover?
Oh no, father.
Lucas' successor
How could it not be Bella Jean?
Now, Lucas trusts
The designer is Bella Jean.
But the owner is Bella Jinbo
Rumor has it that Judy Wong is being targeted.
It was spinning
Because this kind of advanced information is mine...
How can that be?
They say Bella Jean's skills are better.
So who is coming to the event?
- Did you get the list?
- How do you secure the list?
- Because this is enough for me...
- Bella Jean is warm?
- I'm sure it's not coming.
-Why?
- He's on vacation in Malaga.
- Malaga…
- Where is it?
- Spain
Bella Jean every year on vacation
I heard they only go there
And it only goes to one house.
Our editor-in-chief too
They said they went out to play
Anyway, it's there
Ah… Where is Mala?
- I don't know.
- I need to know
Even the editor-in-chief doesn’t know the address.
Well, it's on top of a five-story building.
It went round and round like this
-There is an ice cream shop on the first floor.
- Ice cream…
Why are my eyeballs rolling?
Afraid?
-What are you doing?
- Don't tell me, multiplayer doesn't work.
- Oh! Yes, give me your passport.
-Why the passport?
I have to go see Bella Jean.
Am I the only one going? That far away?
Lonely and lonely?
Do I have any schedule?
I'm Dongwoon's son, the deputy chief?
I'm absent from work today
Uh, 4 days of monthly leave and annual leave.
- Shall we find out Seo Ji-woo’s schedule?
- You turned out to be a total fashion person.
I’m usually a bit of a loser, right?
This is how you spend your precious annual leave?
Haven't we already started?
I guess 5 nights and 6 days is overseas, right?
what?
Who am I talking to now?
What are you going to eat for lunch?
I want marathon soup
What did you say earlier, let's eat pasta?
Let’s eat Chinese food, sorry, let’s eat Chinese food!
Hey, why is the conductor
Leave your seat empty...
Reporter Choi, find a good Chinese restaurant.
To a delicious malatang restaurant
Hey, I'll resign and go to the secretary's office.
Think twice about coming in.
What it means to be sparing is to be trash
Who made it?
The vacation I cherished and cherished
I fell asleep after writing this
Do you know something like that?
Binggrae you son of a bitch?
You're talking about him, right?
The kid isn't that obnoxious.
I guess you haven't met the real bitch.
- Huh?
- No, no.
Uh, let's go
Have a nice trip
Even though they are old
Am I immature?
A bastard called a reporter
Hey, why does Bella Jean do this every year?
I know you're coming here on vacation.
I mean Bella Jean.
Because I’m spending my vacation in such a pretty place
It will just come in smoothly, right?
Is there anyone coming out of the hotel?
But we are going
Isn't it faster?
I think we're almost there
It's here!
- Hello
hello
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello
- Welcome.
It's really nice to meet you.
The accommodation is very close.
please follow me
- Yes
- Follow me.
It's right there
If the accommodation is the host’s house…
There are no hotels around here
I was planning to stay near Bella Jean's accommodation.
I just thought my eyes were falling out
You know? Looking for accommodation
It's not normal
But I use this system
I don’t have good memories of the accommodation I stayed at.
Uh, you can when you catch it
Because I have a discerning eye, things like this
Me on the sea view terrace
I'll let you eat breakfast
It's sea porridge, very
come this way
In this alley atmosphere
The sea view angle is not visible.
It's here
Honey, guests are here.
hello
Welcome to my home.
- Hello
This is the living room
Would you like to come this way?
You can use this room.
There is also a cozy balcony.
you'll love it
thank you
sea view
My excitement is crossing the border.
I'm not excited
I can see the sea
Then you can't see it?
So, what are we here to see, Seaview?
- I came to see Bella Jean.
- Yes
Should we take a look this way?
hmm…
- Where am I?
- That's where we are now, yeah.
‘Amore Gelato’…
This is the bottom part...
- Is this enough?
- Uh
Let me ask you something.
Are there any accommodations in this building?
No, in this building
It's just a store and an office.
yes, thank you
Uh…
Should we go this way?
- Hello
It's on the 3rd floor. Is it because you want to eat?
- Come quickly.
- Child... Yeah
Huh? It's on the 5th floor
Oh, stay here, my legs hurt.
Oh, right?
- It's just a family home, not a dormitory.
- Ah...
Where is the cafe? I will find it.
I think it will come out soon
I'm dying desperately
If my legs hurt
You're going to carry me
That's overkill
- Huh? It's a gelato shop.
- Huh?
- It’s on the 5th floor?
- Hey, I can feel it.
Sit down, I'll come and take a look.
Right?
That's right
Hey, then what about Bella Jean?
Oh, they said they were going to Barcelona and coming tomorrow.
Ah…
It was next to the owner’s house.
I left my contact information
I'll contact you right away when I arrive.
Uh…
Will you really come tomorrow?
- huh?
- Wassi
-Why, why?
- Hey, this is it, just
‘Mr. Godo can’t come today.
They say they'll come tomorrow', but...
- If you don't come, after the play, that's it!
- Quiet
Bella Jean, I can't come today.
But they say tomorrow will definitely come, let’s believe it
Do you know anything? Will you come today?
So, what are we doing today?
See Malaga
Are we on a trip today, okay?
- But if it doesn't come like Godot...
- Oh, really, let's go.
- Hey, you found everything, huh?
- That's right.
- Shall we eat first?
- Right, uh, really?
Let’s go on vacation later too.
In earnest
After seeing the accommodation
how many times do i say
Closest to Bella Jean’s accommodation…
Definitely better accommodation
There must have been
You know my deep intentions
Not until
So what is your deep intention?
The accommodation may feel a bit small.
On the contrary, it's cozy, exotic coziness.
How wide is the bed, a double bed?
If you fall while lying down, you will have a fracture.
Even if two people sleep in a single bed
There was a time when we had plenty, girl.
What should I do?
- Picasso’s birthplace is here.
- I thought you were on a school trip?
Just one beer for a time like this
If you just drink it... It's perfect
- Eat this.
- bite, bite
Don't you think? alcohol?
It’s not that I don’t think about it.
The taste of knowing is the scariest.
Just endure it until you die.
I can do it too
Even if I'm scared of the taste of knowing
If you tolerate it, I can tolerate it too.
let's go
- What should I do, though?
- I heard there’s Picasso’s birthplace.
No, not like that
It's like going to high school.
The two kites are overseas
Did you go on a secret date?
How do you know that?
Did you send me a picture?
uh? me… My heart ached.
kid, just
It's okay to pretend not to know
You can't forget your sister-in-law
I want to reunite
It seemed like he was sincere.
But is your sister-in-law living with you?
That's not it, it's a misunderstanding
I sent someone to find out
Wow, Mr.
Am I right? uh?
They fucked me, right?
What should I do then?
I can't take anyone's side, really.
But brother, you know
I'm salty about him again, huh?
I feel sad just thinking about Seo Ji-woo
My father, Mr.
Seo Ji-woo, if you say it one more time
I said it was a legacy and nothing else, Mr.
I want to live well again
I knelt down saying I wanted to
Wow, that's amazing, you too
‘Chairman Seo is gone too.
Take it back and do something!'
‘What kind of child is this?
'Something that has no basis'
‘I accepted it because I saw Chairman Seo’s face.’
'Take that again, you bastard!'
They said it was like this
What do you mean?
I'm really, I'm Seo Ji-woo
I guess I really loved you, bro.
Who? who is what kind of guy
Are you saying you don't know if it's your child?
Him! Seo Ji-woo
Jarim Apparel Chairman Seo Won-seok
They say she’s not their daughter.
Where is their mom going, huh?
They say it’s the child you gave birth to.
Does that make sense? IC
That's ridiculous, Mr.
Uh, let's go
Oh? Sounds fun.
Oh? Oh, the flea markets of Europe
It must be romantic.
Let's go
What is this, skiing?
uh? Cookies sound delicious
- Hello
- Welcome.
I ate two ice creams
That's right, then go first.
- I'm going to buy some of this.
- Uh
- I see.
- It's 6 euros.
Then with this…
Yes, of course
- How much is this?
- 5 euros.
Hey, is it real?
- Yes
- It’s a woman’s scarf?
- Wasn't I a little fast?
-My hand first...
-Because your arm is long.
yes?
why?
No, this
I think I caught it first
- I caught it at the same time
- Uh, this...
I'm sorry
we caught it first
No one can digest it
It's an item
Then something like this
Who should do it?
To you too
I don't think it suits me
- Jiwoo
- You said you caught it first?
1998 Louis SS
delta series scarf
According to the two-piece pattern
98 limited edition scarves
You know
I ignored it, but I got a feeling.
Who are you?
if… Bella Jean?
Hey
my ace is in malaga
You must be having a hard time
- It's your ace, not mine.
- Is this really going to happen?
Honey, what did you say, Ace?
- Latitude? The name was a bit unusual
- hardness
Not latitude but longitude
Ah, right, right, longitude, longitude
Kim Kyung-do, where is Mr. Kim from?
Not Kyung Kim, not Kyung Lee
Oh, I see, it’s Mr. Lee.
I'm so glad
I get along really well with Mr. Lee.
I saw the tarot
I heard my last name is Lee.
He also has peerless eyes, right?
I'm with a peerless man...
- hey!
- why?
Where is Bella Jean?
Baby, how much am I
Should I do my best?
I investigated everything.
Bella Jean went on vacation
Where did everything go, everything!
There is an ice cream shop on the first floor.
What about a 5-story building?
Is that all?
If you could do that in a foreign country
Can you find someone?
can't you find it?
you are so shameless
I got robbed that much too.
Wait a minute, wait a minute
It's Spanish time now...
Hey, hey, now
Bella Jean It's just time to answer the phone.
Turbidity, stress
Hey, you and that shirt
Do you think that jacket suits you?
You wear whatever you're told to do.
I need to sort that out first.
Hey! Stop talking nonsense
I'll just summarize it for you.
I'm calling Bella Jean now.
give me my ace number
Let Bella Jean contact you first.
Okay? 'Go on'
Hmm, I guess I should go ‘go on’ with this color.
'Go on'
I'm real, I'm real
He is such a pure person.
I believe in friendship and chatter
I even picked up Bella Jean’s location!
'Go on'
If I really get involved with you again
Either hit the editor or something.
quit the friendship
See, I don't accept it.
I'm not that close
How many times do I have to say this...
Oh my Bella
Oh my, where is our Bella?
- Did you get it? Oh, awesome, oh, creepy
- Oh, Barcelona?
Hey, hey, hey, fly to Malaga
Oh my, this is Bella Barcelona.
It’s so nice there, isn’t it?
Hey, don't talk nonsense.
‘High temperature, high temperature, high temperature’
When are you going to Malaga, baby?
Holding on is also a strategy.
- Are you in tears?
- Is it funny?
What a luxury brand
Bring in a designer?
Have you ever liked another girl?
There is
It’s really colorful and novel, Lee Kyung-do
So are you forgetting now too?
Why have we never met?
‘Waiting for Godot’ is also over.
It's all over
They said if I wait, they will come, but that's bullshit
The play is also closing...
We have to end this asshole too.